Guide to the Sturges Kellogg Papers 1856-1864 MS 032 MS 032 MS 032
Cornwall Historical Society
Sturges Kellogg Papers
1856-1864
Cornwall Historical Society
MS 032
0.5 linear feet (1 box)
This collection contains items connected to the related Sturges-Kellogg family.
Provenance
unknown
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
On May 30, 1849, Maria C. Sturges (1831-1904) married Theodore Kellogg (1824-1903) in Sharon, Connecticut. Maria was born in Sharon March 6, 1831 to Lewis Burr Sturges and Charlotte Hunt, and her husband was born September 5, 1824 in Cornwall to Philo Kellogg and Charlotte Miles.
Scope and Content Note
The collection includes letters written by Maria Sturges Kellogg, as well as other members of her family whose exact relationships to her are unknown.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged by subject then chronologically within each subject.
The files are grouped into 2 series:
Correspondence
Miscellaneous
Cornwall (Conn.)--history.; Cornwall (Conn.); Correspondence; article; Cornwall Historical Society; Sturges, Maria C. (1831-1904); Kellogg, Theodore (1824-1903); Cornwall Historical Society
- Correspondence
  - Letter from L.B. Sturges to R.C. Sturges, 1856 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Letter from F.J. Thomas to his uncle, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letter from Cornelia C. Cook to Robert Sturges, regarding Sturges genealogy, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Envelope addressed to Capt. R.C. Sturges at General Hospital No. 1 in Chattanooga, TN, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Letter from Lucius Cook to Robert Sturges, regarding Sturges genealogy, 1859 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Letter from J. S. Sturges to Robert C. Sturges, 1861 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Letter from John H. Lambert to R.C. Sturges, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Letter from Maria Sturges Kellogg to her brother, 1864 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Letter from Elizabeth Sturges to her sister, Maria Sturges Kellogg, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous
  - Article, “Col. McHenry,” in the Louisville Journal, 1862 (Box 1, Folder 10)